Emerson, Lynn Arthur Papers /3053
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lynn Arthur Emerson Papers
1919-1954
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McConnell, John W.
/3053
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Reports and programs relating to the National Youth Administration.
8436141
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Emerson, Lynn A. (Lynn Arthur), 1890-
8436141
- Reports and programs relating to the National Youth Administration. (Box 1)
  - Pullman School Survey, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Survey Report Pullman Free School of Manual Training, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administration, Instruction, and Guidance Bergen County Vocational and Technical High School, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NYA - Vocational Relationships, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National Youth Administration, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - National Youth Administration Policy Planning Staff Conference Memos, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reports of Visits to NYA Projects 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - National Youth Administration Residence Project Quoddy Village, Maine, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - National Youth Administration for Louisiana, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - New Haven Survey (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Education for Industry - "The Changing Rural School", 1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Education, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Summer Session - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Summer Session Planning -- 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - National Youth Administration, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Vocational Industrial Education in New Haven, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Photos - Leaders in Ind. Educ. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Education and Proposed Development in the I.L.R. School, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Reports and programs relating to the National Youth Administration. (Box 2)
  - Portland, Oregon - Survey of Carpenters (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Teacher Training Course, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stenotype Report of Meeting of Working Comm. Feb. 1944 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Study of Technical Institute Education, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Need for State University Lynn A. Emerson, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Arkansas Survey, 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vita Miscellaneous (Agenda, Announcements, Ballots, Photo, Lists), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Vita Club, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Penziner, Bernard A. 1402 East Moyamensing Avenue, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Vita Constitutions, Certificates of Membership, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vita - Advisory Committee, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Vita 1952 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Vita Dinner at Joe's Material, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Vita Announcements 1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Speakers for Vita, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Vita - Finances, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - V.I.T.A. - Treasury Reports 1950- (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Industrial License Requirements by States, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Teacher Training, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Methods and Techniques, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Methods and Techniques, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 20)